famousquotesandauthors.com 2016-06-08

# Privacy Statement

| 

Privacy Statement

FamousQuotesAndAuthors.com has created this Privacy Statement to explain how we collect, use and share information we gather about you and how we will protect your personal privacy within our website (http://www.famousquotesandauthors.com/).

**Use of Cookies**  
Our website use cookies to enhance your experience while using our website. Cookies are small text files of information that some websites transfer to the computer that is browsing that website and are used for record-keeping purposes at many websites. Use of cookies makes web-surfing easier by performing certain functions such as saving your passwords, your personal preferences regarding your use of the particular website and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to save the quotations you have placed in your "Favorite Quotes List" section on the website. Many consider the use of cookies to be an industry standard.

Your browser is probably set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our Site will not function properly when you view them.

**Advertisers**  
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**IP Addresses**  
An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are browsing the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website, analyze trends, track users' movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the website. An IP address does not contain any personally identifiable information.

**Children's Privacy**  
FamousQuotesAndAuthors.com is committed to protecting the safety and privacy of children and teenagers using the Internet. We do not knowingly collect or use any information from children under the age of 13 and we believe that children should consult their parents before giving out any personally identifiable information.

**Links to Other Sites**  
FamousQuotesAndAuthors.com contains links to other websites. Please be aware that FamousQuotesAndAuthors.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other websites. We encourage our visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personal information from you. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by FamousQuotesAndAuthors.com.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
From time to time we may update this Privacy Statement and will post a notice of any significant changes on our website. Please check our Privacy Statement periodically to be aware of the last changes and additions.

**Contacting the Website**  
If you have any comments or questions on the above privacy statement, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.famousquotesandauthors.com/contact_us.html) at any time. Your opinion is very important to us.

*This Privacy Statement was last updated on January 16, 2010.

|  | Quote of the Day  
---  
I am not bound to win, but I am bound to be true. I am not bound to succeed, but I am bound to live up to what light I have.   
  
Top 10 Authors  
---  

 View All Popular Authors
